After 8 years of discussions with Calvin
[music] today I finally logged in.
Because yesterday's baptism video was so popular,
I'll tell you what we were doing.
I am Catholic and Calvin Christian.
We've been together since 2018 and 3 months
ago I finally got proposed to.  So because
we agreed to have a Christian marriage,
last May I decided to get baptized.
It looks calm in the video.  But
honestly, I was really nervous because this was my first
time.  But luckily
my family and Kalvin's family
came to support us.  Even Kalvin brought
this beautiful bouquet of flowers.  That day,
all baptism participants were asked to wear
dark clothes but covered with a white robe.
The event began, we sang, listened to
the sermon, then one by one we were called
[music] to be baptized.  And when my name
was called, honestly my heart wanted to jump out of my chest.  But
it turned out to be really fast.  After
baptism, I felt relieved.
After that, I immediately took a photo with Calvin.
Yes, in wet condition.  And it turned out that
my little sister brought a hair dryer.
So my mom let me dry my hair
in the church lobby, she said she was afraid I would get a
headache.  The point is that that day I was
grateful to have been born again and to have the same
faith as Calvin.  Follow for
our other wedding preparation videos.